hsbcapply.com 2007-06-29

# HSBC Privacy and Security Policy

Privacy | Privacy Statement | How to Request That Your Information Not Be Shared | Security Information | Website Terms and Conditions

HSBC Bank Nevada, N.A., ("HSBC Bank Nevada") is the proud issuer of the HSBC Credit Card. We understand the importance of handling customer information in a professional and confidential manner. We know that privacy is an important element of our customers' confidence in us and we understand that our customers expect us to collect and retain personal financial information responsibly. 

Experience

  * HSBC Bank Nevada is a member of a financial family with more than a century of financial experience.

Electronic, Physical and Administrative Safeguards

  * We take great care to ensure your personal information is kept safe.
  * Only carefully trained professionals and companies who service your account or who provide services to you or to us have access to your personal information.
  * HSBC Bank Nevada diligently maintains security measures that comply with applicable federal standards. This assists us in preventing unauthorized access to your non-public personal information. 

Responsible Information Sharing

  * Information is sometimes shared within the HSBC Bank Nevada family of Affiliates for purposes that could benefit you such as fraud control and other general business purposes. 
  * We only contract with respectable, carefully screened third-party financial and non-financial companies that offer our customers valuable merchandise and services. 

Control Over Information Sharing

  * We give you a choice. If you do not want us to share your information, follow our opt-out procedures and we'll be happy to comply with your opt-out request, consistent with the procedures in our Privacy Statement. 
  * Click here to view our Privacy Statement and How to Request That Your Information Not Be Shared.
  * Click here to view Security Information.
  * Click here for information on our use of "cookie" technology.
  * Click here for Website Terms and Conditions.

Our Commitment to You | Types of Information We Collect | We Respect Your Privacy | How We Share Information with Our Affiliates* | How We Share Information Outside the HSBC Bank Nevada Family | Privacy and Security on the Internet

Our Commitment to You

HSBC Bank Nevada, N.A., is proud to be part of a financial services organization that has been providing superior products and services to its customers for more than a century. We greatly appreciate the trust that you and millions of other customers have placed in us, and we protect that trust by respecting your privacy, even if our relationship with you ends.

This Privacy Statement illustrates our commitment to your privacy and explains our privacy practices so you can make an informed decision about whom you allow us to share your information with in order to offer you additional products and services. Although most customers enjoy receiving offers and information about additional products and services, if you prefer that we do not share your information for marketing purposes, we will respect your choice. If you have selected a credit insurance product, the privacy statement applicable to that credit insurance product is set forth at the end of this Privacy Statement.

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

Types of Information We Collect

It is important for you to know that in order to ensure that our customers get the very best service and the highest quality products, HSBC Bank Nevada collects demographic information (such as your name and address) and credit information (such as information related to your Accounts with us and others). This information comes either directly from you, for instance, from your application and transactions on your Account; or, it may come from an outside source such as your credit bureau report. In addition, if you visit our Internet website, we may collect certain information about your Internet usage. Gathering this information helps us to identify our customers and manage our customer relationships. It also assists us in the development of products and services to meet the continuing needs of our customers.

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

We Respect Your Privacy

Since some of the information we gather is not publicly available, we take great care to ensure that this information is kept safe from unauthorized access. Because HSBC Bank Nevada respects your privacy and values your trust, the only employees or companies who can access your nonpublic personal information are those who use it to service your Account or provide services to you or to us. HSBC Bank Nevada diligently maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal standards to guard your non-public personal information and to assist us in preventing unauthorized access to that information.

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Share Information with Our Affiliates*

From time to time, for general business purposes such as fraud control, or when we think it may benefit you, we share certain information with other companies within our corporate family (i.e., Affiliates). These companies all provide financial services such as banking, consumer finance, insurance, mortgage, and brokerage services. Some examples include companies doing business under the names Household, Beneficial, or HSBC. We may also share certain information with non-financial service providers that become our Affiliates (such as travel, auto and shopping clubs). The information we share might come from your application, such as your name, address, telephone number, Social Security number, and e-mail address. Also, the information we share could include your transactions with us or our Affiliates (such as your Account balance, payment history, and parties to the transaction), your Internet usage, or credit card usage. Except for Vermont residents, the information we share with our Affiliates may also include your assets, income, or credit reports, which we collect from the sources described above. With this information, our Affiliates can determine if the products they specialize in, such as mortgages, automobile loans and insurance, may be of benefit to you.

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Share Information Outside the HSBC Bank Nevada Family

Except for California and Vermont residents, we also may share information with companies outside our corporate family (non-Affiliates) that are able to extend special offers we feel might be of value to you. These companies may be financial service providers (such as mortgage bankers or insurance product providers) or they may be non-financial companies (such as retailers or marketing companies). These offers are typically for products and services that you might not otherwise hear about. The information we may provide them comes from the sources described above and might include your name, address, and phone number. For California and Vermont residents, state law restricts how we share information about you, and we have chosen not to share your information in this way.

We may also provide information to non-Affiliates that perform operational services related to your Account or marketing services for us. Sharing information with these types of companies is permitted by law. Such a company might include a financial company (such as a mortgage banker or insurance service provider) with whom we have a joint marketing agreement or a non-financial company (such as a data processor or Internet service provider) with whom we have a service agreement. The information we may share also comes from the sources described above and might include your name, address, phone number and Account history with us.

Finally, we provide information about you to non-Affiliates such as credit reporting agencies and companies which provide services related to your Account. This information sharing is also permitted by law.

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

Privacy and Security on the Internet

Our website, hsbccreditcard.com, offers you the opportunity to view you current Account information and make payments online, in addition to providing general information about our company and products. You may view information about Internet Security by clicking here.

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

Privacy  |   Privacy Statement  |   How to Request That Your Information Not Be Shared  |   
Security Information  |   Website Terms and Conditions

Information Sharing with Our Affiliates* | Information Sharing with Non-Affiliates

Information Sharing with Our Affiliates*

If you do not want us to share your credit information (such as your credit bureau information) with our Affiliates, please let us know by completing the opt-out reply form. We will be happy to comply with your request. If you have previously informed us of your preference, you do not need to do so again. Your request will not apply to information about your transactions or experience with us (such as Account information, Account usage, or payment history) and will only apply to the HSBC credit card Account you have designated on the opt-out form by Account number. An opt-out request by any party on a joint Account will apply to all parties on the joint Account. 

Top of How To Request That Your Information Not Be Shared  
Back to Top

Information Sharing with Non-Affiliates

If you do not want us to share your non-public personal information with non-Affiliates (unless we are permitted or required by law to do so), you will also need to indicate your request by completing the opt-out reply form. We will be happy to comply with your request. If you have previously informed us of your preference, you do not need to do so again. Please understand that your request may exclude you from receiving valuable offers in the future. Your request will only apply to the HSBC credit card Account you have designated on the opt-out form by Account number. An opt-out request by any party on a joint Account will apply to all parties on the joint Account. Opt-out requests will not apply to information sharing that is permitted by law. 

Once you have completed the reply form, please mail it to HSBC Card Services, P.O. Box 60173, City of Industry, CA 91716-0173. Please allow sufficient time for us to process your request. 

_**Please do not include any other correspondence with your request.**_

* "Affiliates" are companies that are related to us by common ownership or corporate control. Our Affiliates include HFC®, Beneficial®, HSBC Auto Finance Inc., Household Insurance Group Holding Company., and HSBC companies such as HSBC Bank USA, N.A. and HSBC Mortgage Corporation. 

Top of How To Request That Your Information Not Be Shared  
Back to Top

**HOUSEHOLD INSURANCE GROUP HOLDING COMPANY**  
Privacy Statement for Customers with Insurance Products**

**Introduction - Our Commitment to You**

Household Insurance Group Holding Company ("HIG") is proud to be part of a financial services organization that has been providing superior products and services to its customers for more than 150 years. We greatly appreciate the trust that you and millions of customers have placed in us, and we will protect that trust by continuing to respect the privacy of all our applicants and customers even if our formal customer relationship ends. 

**How We Handle Information We Obtain**

It is important for you to know that in order to ensure that our customers get the very best service and the highest quality products, HIG collects demographic information (like your name and address) and information related to your insurance coverage (like insurance application information). This information comes either directly from you, for instance, from your application, or from your transactions with us. In addition, if you visit our Internet website, we may collect certain information about your Internet usage.

Because some of the information we gather is not publicly available, we take great care to ensure that this information is kept safe from unauthorized access, and we will not share the information in violation of any regulation or law. HIG diligently maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal standards to guard your private personal information and to assist us in preventing unauthorized access to that information.

If you have selected insurance or another product offered by HIG, the Privacy Statement is set forth herein and is applicable to information used by HIG in connection with the insurance or other product you purchased. HIG does not disclose information about you to HIG's affiliates or to third parties, except as permitted by law.

We reserve the right to change our privacy practices at any time in accordance with applicable law. Notice of such changes will be provided if required by applicable law.

** Household Insurance Group Holding Company (also under the trade name of HSBC Insurance Services or HSBC Insurance) includes Household Insurance Group, Inc., Household Life Insurance Company, HSBC Insurance Company of Delaware (formerly known as Service General Insurance Company), First Central National Life Insurance Company of New York, Household Life Insurance of Delaware, BFC Insurance Agency of Nevada, HSBC Insurance Agency (USA) Inc., and such other companies Household Insurance Group Holding Company may subsequently acquire.

Updates and Modifications: This Privacy Statement was last updated on April 10, 2007. We reserve the right to modify our privacy practices at any time. Any such modification will be communicated to you in accordance with applicable law. 

Top of How To Request That Your Information Not Be Shared  
Back to Top

Privacy | Privacy Statement |  How to Request That Your Information Not Be Shared | Security Information | Website Terms and Conditions

We understand that security is a prime concern for our customers, and our website strives to offer a high level of security: 

  * All Internet access must be completed using a browser that supports SSL encryption. All communications between you and our website are encrypted by a 128 bit secure link to protect the confidentiality of your data. State of the art monitoring systems and firewalls are used to prevent unauthorized access to our systems.
  * Users are required to select their own Login ID and Password when they sign up, and can change it at any time. 
  * The website will automatically log off after a period of inactivity during any session to protect your information.
  * Only carefully trained professionals and companies who service your account have access to your personal information.
  * We diligently maintain security measures that comply with applicable federal standards.

Top of Security Information  
Back to Top

Privacy | Privacy Statement | How to Request That Your Information Not Be Shared | Security Information | Website Terms and Conditions

Copyright and Other Intellectual Property | Limited Liability | NO WARRANTIES | Links | Children | Confidentiality of Information | Information and Cookies | Choice of Law | Website Content and Material | Waiver and Severability | Access to Secured Areas

Copyright and Other Intellectual Property

HSBC Bank Nevada, or its corporate parents, affiliated companies, or subsidiaries (collectively "HSBC Bank Nevada" and/or its Affiliates") is the owner or the authorized user of this website and certain other websites linked to the site, as well as all text, images, graphics, photos, animation, music, sounds and other materials contained within these websites.

The materials contained within these websites, including, without limitation, any copyrights, trademarks, service marks, and all other proprietary materials, are protected by the U.S. and international copyright laws and treaty provisions, trademark laws, and other proprietary rights laws. The material contained within these websites is provided by HSBC Bank Nevada and/or its Affiliates only for lawful uses by customers, employees, and members of the general public. The material may not be copied, republished, incorporated into another website or reproduced (whether by linking, framing, or any other method), transmitted, distributed, uploaded, posted, used to create a derivative work or exploited in any other way without the express written consent of HSBC Bank Nevada.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Limited Liability

NEITHER HSBC BANK NEVADA, ITS PARENT, AFFILIATES OR SUBSIDIARIES, OR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THE INFORMATION AT THIS SITE, NOR THE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR REPRESENTATIVES OF ANY OF THE FOREGOING, ARE LIABLE IN ANY WAY FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST PROFITS, COST OF PROCURING SUBSTITUTE SERVICE OR LOST OPPORTUNITY) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS SITE OR THE USE OF THIS SITE OR A LINKED SITE OR WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE OR A LINKED SITE, WHETHER OR NOT HSBC BANK NEVADA IS MADE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS LIMITATION INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, THE TRANSMISSION OF ANY VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES OR HARMFUL CODE THAT MAY AFFECT A USER'S EQUIPMENT, ANY INCOMPATIBILITY BETWEEN THIS SITE'S FILES AND THE USER'S BROWSER OR OTHER SITE ACCESSING PROGRAM, FAILURE OF ANY ELECTRONIC OR TELEPHONE EQUIPMENT, COMMUNICATION OR CONNECTION LINES, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, THEFT, OPERATOR ERRORS, OR ANY FORCE MAJEURE. HSBC BANK NEVADA DOES NOT GUARANTEE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO THIS SITE OR A LINKED SITE. THE CONTENT, ACCURACY, OPINIONS EXPRESSED, AND OTHER LINKS PROVIDED BY THE LINKED SITES ARE NOT INVESTIGATED, VERIFIED, MONITORED OR ENDORSED BY HSBC BANK NEVADA. THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND DESCRIPTION OF SERVICES PUBLISHED ON THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS, AND HSBC BANK NEVADA SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY FOR SUCH INACCURACIES OR ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY MADE TO THE INFORMATION ON THE SITE AND LINKED SITES. HSBC BANK NEVADA MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS OR CHANGES TO THE SITE AT ANY TIME.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

NO WARRANTIES

ALL PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND CONTENT ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY, OR ACCURACY. NEITHER HSBC BANK NEVADA NOR ITS PARENT, AFFILIATES OR SUBSIDIARIES ENDORSES AND NONE ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY INFORMATION ON THIS SITE. IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS AND COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON THIS SITE. HSBC BANK NEVADA SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY DUTY TO UPDATE THE INFORMATION ON THE SITE.

USER AGREES TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND, AND HOLD HSBC BANK NEVADA HARMLESS FROM ANY LIABILITY, LOSS, CLAIM AND EXPENSE, INCLUDING ATTORNEY'S FEES RELATED TO A USER'S VIOLATION OF THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE USE OF THE SERVICES AND INFORMATION PROVIDED AT THIS SITE. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Links

Clicking on certain links within this website or certain other websites that are linked to this website may take you to other websites, or may display information on your computer screen from other websites, which are not maintained by HSBC Bank Nevada. Such websites may contain terms and conditions, privacy provisions, confidentiality provisions, or other provisions that differ from the terms and conditions applicable to this website. Links to other Internet services and websites are provided solely for the convenience of users. A link to any service or website is not an endorsement of any kind of the service or website, its content, or its sponsoring organization.

HSBC BANK NEVADA AND ITS CORPORATE PARENTS, AFFILIATES, AND SUBSIDIARIES ASSUME NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR THE CONTENT, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR OPINIONS EXPRESSED IN A WEBSITE, TO WHICH THIS SITE IS LINKED (A "LINKED SITE") AND SUCH LINKED SITES ARE NOT MONITORED, INVESTIGATED, OR CHECKED FOR ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS BY HSBC BANK NEVADA. IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS AND COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON A LINKED SITE. ALL PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND CONTENT OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY, OR ACCURACY.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Children

HSBC Bank Nevada does not knowingly market to, or solicit, or collect personal information from children under age 18.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Confidentiality of Information

HSBC Bank Nevada has taken reasonable steps to ensure the confidentiality of information taken at this website and transmitted via the Internet. HSBC Bank Nevada uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. During an SSL session, data passed back and forth between your computer and the HSBC Bank Nevada online card server is secured by using public key cryptography. Your computer exchanges key information with HSBC Bank Nevada computers to create a private conversation that only your computer and HSBC Bank Nevada's system can understand. However, unexpected changes in technology may be used by unauthorized third parties to intercept confidential information and we cannot be responsible should confidential information be intercepted and subsequently used by an unintended recipient. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Information and Cookies

HSBC Bank Nevada may collect and receive the URL you came from, the pages of HSBC Bank Nevada website that were viewed during a visit, the advertisements you clicked, any search terms that you entered to reach our site, and certain other information regarding your internet use. See HSBC Bank Nevada's Privacy Statement for how this information may be used, click here to view Privacy Statement. Some of HSBC Bank Nevada's websites may also make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity, determine how you arrived at our site and maintain your identity as you navigate through the website. HSBC Bank Nevada's websites require cookies to allow you to view your statements and transactions online. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. Cookies make visiting a website easier for you by saving your preferences while you are at the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at many websites. HSBC Bank Nevada uses the information from cookies to provide services that are customized to your needs.

HSBC Bank Nevada may also use third party advertising companies to serve HSBC Bank Nevada's ads on the Internet. These third party advertising companies also employ cookie technology to measure the effectiveness of ads. To do so, these companies may use information about your visits to HSBC Bank Nevada's website and other websites. Unless otherwise notified, these advertising companies do not use names, addresses, e-mail addresses or telephone numbers, and do not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. The use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policy. 

If you want to prevent a third party advertiser from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network's website individually and opt-out.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Choice of Law

All website activity or use and these Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of the United States of America and the laws of the State of Nevada, without regard to conflict of law principles.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Website Content and Material

The information and materials contained in this website, including but not limited to these Terms and Conditions and any product information, are subject to change without notice. Users are deemed to be apprised of and bound by any such changes. Not all products and services are available in all geographic areas. Your eligibility for particular products and services is subject to final determination and acceptance by HSBC Bank Nevada. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Waiver and Severability

Any waiver of any provision contained in these Terms and Conditions shall not be deemed to be a waiver of any other right, term or provision of these Terms and Conditions. If any provision in these Terms and Conditions shall be or become wholly or partially invalid, illegal or unenforceable, such provision shall be enforced to the extent it is legal and valid and the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions shall in no way be affected or impaired thereby.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Access to Secured Areas

Access to and use of password protected and/or secure areas of this website is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized persons attempting to access these areas of the website may be subject to prosecution.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Updates: These Terms and Conditions were last updated April 10, 2007. Please check periodically for changes.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Privacy  |   Privacy Statement  |   How to Request That Your Information Not Be Shared  |   
Security Information  |   Website Terms and Conditions
